wilcom.com 2016-04-15

# Privacy Statement

## Wilcom Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to Wilcom International Pty Limited and all references to " **Wilcom** ", " **we** ", " **us** " or " **our** " are references to Wilcom International Pty Limited (ACN 119 508 575).

Wilcom is committed to protecting your privacy.  This Privacy Policy sets out how we manage your personal information and other information.  From time to time, we may need to change this Privacy Policy.  If we do so, we will post the updated version on our website (www.wilcom.com/about/PrivacyStatement.aspx) and it will apply to all your information held by us at the time.

When we refer to your information, we are referring to your personal information (as defined under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)) and other information about you.

### The kind of information we collect and hold about you

Depending on the particular circumstances, we may collect and hold different information about you.  For example, this may include:

  * your name, date of birth, occupation, home or work address, telephone and email contact details;
  * financial information, such as your bank account or credit card details;
  * your Wilcom security credentials, such as username and passwords;
  * your website address and domain name;
  * information about how you use our products and services; and
  * where necessary, additional information as part of our user authentication process.

### How we collect your information

We may collect your information in a number of ways, including: 

  * directly from you (for example, where you provide information to us or our representatives on the telephone or in person, when you apply for our products and services online);
  * from third parties such as our related companies, business partners, clients and other service providers;
  * from publicly available sources of information; and
  * from our records and databases.

We may also collect information from you online using cookies and other analytical tools or when you visit our websites, including when you use our products and services.

### How we hold your information

We take reasonable steps to maintain the security of your information and to protect it from unauthorised disclosure.  When your financial details (such as a credit card number) are transmitted from our website to a third party website, they are protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

However, as the internet is not always secure, we cannot be responsible for the security of information you transmit over the internet or for any unauthorised access or use of that information.

You should also be aware that any personal information you disclose when using our online forums will be available to the public. You should take appropriate care to safeguard your information by not disclosing your security credentials (such as your username and password).

### How we use and disclose your information

We may use and disclose your information for a range of different purposes, including:

  * to provide products and services and information about those products and services to you, to assist you with enquiries, or to improve our customer service;
  * for our billing and account purposes;
  * to maintain our business relationships where you are a business partner, a user of our website and services, or a customer;
  * to our related companies, our business partners, distributors and service providers, and other third parties who assist us in providing services to you and managing our business;
  * to our professional advisers; and
  * where required by law.

We may disclose or give access to your information to our related companies and our service providers who are located outside of Australia.  For example, we may disclose your information to our related companies and business partners in the countries listed at http://www.wilcom.com/en-us/contact/wilcomdistributors.aspx.

### Marketing

We may also use your information so that we, our related companies, and other business partners and service providers can promote and market products, services and special offers, and advise you of news and industry updates, events, reports and other information that we think will be of interest to you. This marketing may be carried in a variety of ways (including by email, SMS/MMS, social media or via our website) and may continue indefinitely until you opt-out by contacting us 61 2 9578 5100 or by email at support@wilcom.com.

### How to assess or correct your personal information

If you wish to access any of your personal information that we hold or would like to correct any errors in that personal information, please contact us using the contact details set out below.  We may charge you an administrative fee for providing access to your personal information in response to a request.

### How to contact us or make a privacy complaint

If you have any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy or how we manage your information, you can contact on 61 2 9578 5100 or by email at [support@wilcom.com](mailto:support@wilcom.com)

If we are unable to resolve any complaints you may have, you may wish to contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner by calling 1300 363 992 or visiting [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/).
